[GRUNTS]
- Excuse me.
- Mm-hm.
[GRUNTS]
- What is wrong with you?
- I'm helping you with Stephanie.
(Leonard:)By making constipated moose sounds?
When I fail to open this and you succeed,
it will establish you as the alpha male.
(Sheldon:)You see, when a female witnesses
an exhibition of physical domination...
(Sheldon:)...she produces the hormone oxytocin.
If the two of you engage in intercourse,
this will create the biochemical reaction...
...which laypeople naively interpret
as falling in love.
(Steph:)Huh.
(Leonard:)Would it work
if I just punched you in the face?
(Sheldon:)Yes, actually, it would,
but let's see how the lid goes.
(Sheldon:)I'm not strong enough, Leonard.
You'll have to do it.
(Leonard:)- God's sakes.
- Go ahead, it's pre-loosened.